

FRONT END DEVELOPER

Details

Morecambe Close Stevenage, SG1 2AZ UK 07687654323 supriya2872@gmail.com

NATIONALITY

Indian

DATE / PLACE OF BIRTH

28th July 1992 Maharashtra

Links

GitHub

Skills

HTML/CSS/JavaScript

jQuery

Django

Git

Angular

MySQL

sketch

Docker

Amazon AWS

Hobbies

Coocking Research on latest Design

Profile

Experienced Front-End Web Developer with over 3.5 year of experience planning, coding, testing, deploying and maintaining websites. Skilled in designing, developing and testing multiple websites incorporating a range of technologies. Knowledge of Deploying and managing websites using AWS, Panel Secure, Docker.

Employment History

Web Developer, Freelancer, Mumbai

FEBRUARY 2019 - NOVEMBER 2020

- Developed websites using HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Bootstrap
- Implemented enhancements that improved web functionality and responsiveness.
- Designed and maintained client websites, using Angular, Django Framework and content management systems including Magento.
- Deployed and manage websites on AWS (Amazon Web Services)

Front End Developer, GoPBN Pvt.Ltd, Mumbai

JULY 2017 - JANUARY 2019

- Responsible for working on a range of projects, designing websites and interacting on a daily basis with graphic designers, back-end developers.
- Designed and maintained websites, using Bootstrap, Gridder, Angular and content management systems including WordPress, Shopify.
- Presented web-site mock-ups to clients to give them better view Experience.

Education

B.SC.IT, Sikkim Manipal University, Mumbai

JULY 2014 - FEBRUARY 2017

IT, DR.D.Y.Patil College of Engineering, Mumbai

JUNE 2008 - NOVEMBER 2011

Courses

Sketch, Udemy

2021 - 2021

Angular, Udemy

2020 - 2020

JUNE 2021 - JUNE 2021

References

Sumit Sontakke from TCS

smsontakke4@gmail.com | 07405424772

Extra-curricular activities

JUNE 2021 - JUNE 2021